Here I come again to teach y'all about the realities of your parasocial relationships.
Listen close. You supporting somebody by going to their shows or buying their books or buying
their music does not mean that they have to support you. It does not mean that they
owe you anything. The exchange was their art or their skill and your money or barter etc. That
was the exchange. Like I just got an email from somebody saying I can't believe after all the
support I've given you with my hard-earned money for years you blocked me on Instagram. My Instagram
boundary has become very basic. If you are not adding information or supporting what I'm saying
you're blocked. Taking that personal is wild because you know more about the people that you
are following and supporting than they know about you. So the reflection point here is
what did I say and how could I have said it differently or
hmm you know it's hard for Amanda to tell who's who on this internet. Not you owe me the space to speak
how I want to because I've persisted or supported your work. I don't owe you s**t. The exchange already
took place. I do not owe you space on Mark Zuckerberg's free internet page to speak your
mind as you see fit if it annoys me. I know life is tough. You're damn rude eh?
You're right.